<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[StrategyLeadExecute]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[StrategyLeadExecute]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/geraldebenezer/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2016 10:07:34 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/geraldebenezer/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>I find that whenever I am asked to provide a proposal, there is one of two reasons. Either there is a business challenge that needs to be overcome or the company is doing really well and there are lots of opportunities in front of them and the team needs additional training to bring forward their skill-sets. Which one would it be for you? </p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/geraldebenezer/i-find-that-whenever-i-am-asked-to-provide-a-proposal-there/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">97cdec23-58b8-4c65-a518-ea5f7521f379</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2016 10:07:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/6d0e58df-4933-417e-8726-12740c96cf37.png">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/geraldebenezer/management-20/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">dfc2efff-fff9-4744-a47c-72b46496f082</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 03:34:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Becoming a person of influence. Establishing trust with your team is the foundation of a healthy working relationship. I have heard the comment "I dont trust my boss; I dont trust A, I dont trust the company" too many times in the last two decades of my work life. The lack of trust has been shown to impact employee engagement and thus undermining energy and commitment at the individual and team level. What are the factors that undermine trust in the leader? How does a leader behave to engender trust with their team members? </p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/geraldebenezer/becoming-a-person-of-influence-establishing-trust-with-your/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cc566623-2de4-40e9-a5f4-064ba146caca</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2016 05:01:13 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Becoming a person of influence. If you are a Manager, how do you communicate your mission and vision to your people. The ideal way is to ensure that the people had a say in the departmental objectives and plans at the outset. In the event that this was not the case, how do you build this ownership in a practical way? I suggest three steps : 1) Cast the vision 2) Help to establish the link between their personal goals and departmental objectives 2) Trust your people to rise to the challenge 3) Coach to excellence. It may seem like an oversimplication but this is all you need assuming that the people have the skills required to do the job. Among the four steps, which one would you say is the most challenging to do?</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/geraldebenezer/becoming-a-person-of-influence-if-you-are-a-manager-how-do/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a1df40d3-3d9b-47eb-b566-e402ef0bb223</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2016 03:54:49 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Becoming a person of influence. Its easy to talk about influence when you have the power to sanction or offer rewards. What happens if these well-accepted organizational "tools" were taken away from you. How would you lead in this situation? What other tools can you muster and administer in your role in the absence of these tools? In my view, the most effective person is one who uses the standard organizational tools as a last resort in any situation. What are the other tools that you have at your disposal then? In this article, I suggest some perspectives to consider. In this article, we talk about positive psychology. Positive psychology is an extremely powerful tool and is very appealing in many various organizational contexts - goal setting, delegating tasks, mid-year reviews, performance appraisals. A powerful way of thinking is to use the Golden circle approach popularized by Simon Sinek - the Why, How & What. Many a times managers default to the "What" - I want this to be done without talking about the Why and the How. This is the cause of many </p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/geraldebenezer/becoming-a-person-of-influence-its-easy-to-talk-about-influ/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">223f6d98-6c96-435d-8a03-7db73420eec3</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2016 17:06:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Becoming a person of influence. How do you apply the Golden Circle if you are Manager. Its to let your team know what you believe in within the overall context of the organizational mission and vision. In the unlikely case that the mission and vision is incongruent with what you believe in, then you are probably at a cross-road where a decision has to be made - stay on or leave amicably. How do you communicate what you believe in? There are a couple of factors to consider - what makes you inspiring? , what makes you unique?, what are your strengths?, what are your vulnerabilities?, what makes you human?, what makes you trustworthy?, what makes you a leader?, why should others believe in you? A practical way to do this is through story-telling.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/geraldebenezer/becoming-a-person-of-influence-how-do-you-apply-the-golden/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">024b17a0-5c76-4905-a9eb-9eac3e1feb54</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2016 17:05:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What is the value of a Phd to an organizational consultant? Well the answer is, "It depends"..on a number of things. Firstly, how does the the Phd contribute to what the consultant is doing- does it add to the credibility and competence of the consultant in his or her area of expertise. Secondly, can the results be used to improve organizational performance?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>What is the value of a Phd to an organizational consultant? Well the answer is, "It depends"..on a number of things. Firstly, how does the the Phd contribute to what the consultant is doing- does it add to the credibility and competence of the consultant in his or her area of expertise. Secondly, can the results be used to improve organizational performance?</h1>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/geraldebenezer/what-is-the-value-of-a-phd-to-an-organizational-consultant/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">77fc8f3c-c061-479a-8256-740ad9884171</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 05:06:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/5fdba585b8fed4ea12d540b01beae4f3b84fdbe8.png" alt="" title="">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/geraldebenezer/unlocking-the-potential-within/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cbc40f61-aa1f-41e8-8a54-52798c139fee</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 02:47:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>https://youtu.be/owORxKqX0nU</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/geraldebenezer/httpsyoutubeoworxkqx0nu/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3222a309-0ac9-473a-9b22-f34e6805a138</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2016 10:05:25 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[I am a fan of Dr Heidi Grant Halvorson research in motivation science. She talks of the prevalence of two mindsets - one is the " Be Good" mindset and the other "Get Better" mindset. Based on numerous experiments, research concludes that those with the "Get Better" mindset outperform the one with the "Be Good" mindset. The question is how do you cultivate the "Get Better" mindset?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>I am a fan of Dr Heidi Grant Halvorson research in motivation science. She talks of the prevalence of two mindsets - one is the " Be Good" mindset and the other "Get Better" mindset. Based on numerous experiments, research concludes that those with the "Get Better" mindset outperform the one with the "Be Good" mindset. The question is how do you cultivate the "Get Better" mindset?</h1>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/geraldebenezer/i-am-a-fan-of-dr-heidi-grant-halvorson-research-in-motivatio/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">384cb7c5-42d7-4dd5-aec2-556c1dac3027</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2016 09:54:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>